Let's look at a basic model of
我们来看
an artificial neural network where we have only a single hidden layer.
人工神经网络的一个基础模型 该模型只有一个简单的隐藏层
The inputs are each connected to the neurons in
每个输入都分别与隐藏层的各神经元相连
the hidden layer and the neurons in the hidden layer are each
而这些神经元
connected to the neurons in the output layer where
又分别与输出层的各神经元相连
each neuron there represents a single output.
而输出层的每个神经元分别代表着一个输出
We can look at it as a collection of mathematical functions.
我们可以将这个网络看成一个数学函数集
Each input is connected mathematically to
每个输入都以一定的数学关系
a hidden layer of neurons through a set of weights we need
通过一系列权重与隐藏层的神经元相连
to modify and each hidden layer neuron is connected to the output layer in a similar way.
而权重是我们需要调整的对象 隐藏层的每个神经元又以类似的方式与输出层相连
There is no limit to the number of inputs,
无论是输入、
number of hidden neurons in a layer and number of outputs,
隐藏层的神经元还是输出 都没有数量限制
nor are there any correlations between those numbers.
这些数字之间也没有任何相关性
So, we can have n inputs,
所以我们可以有 n 个输入
m hidden neurons and k outputs.
m 个隐藏神经元和 k 个输出
In a closer even more simplistic look,
更具体通俗地来看
we can see that each input is multiplied by
每个输入会与
its corresponding weight and added at the next layers neuron with a bias as well.
相应的权重相乘 然后在下一层的神经元里与偏置相加
The bias is an external parameter of the neuron and can
偏置是神经元的外部参数
be modeled by adding an external fixed value input.
可以用外部固定输入值进行建模
This entire summation will usually go through
这整个运算的和通常会输入到
an activation function to the next layer or to the output.
一个激活函数中 从而进入下一层或输出层
But what is our goal?
但这样做的目的是什么呢？
We can look at our system as a black box that has n inputs and k outputs.
我们可以把整个系统看成一个黑盒子 盒子里有 n 个输入 k 个输出
Our goal is to design the system in such a way that it will give us the correct output y,
我们的目的就是设计一个系统 使其在输入 x 时
for a specific input x.
能正确输出对应的 y
Our job is to decide what's inside this black box.
我们要做的就是决定黑盒子里应该装什么
We know that we will use artificial neural networks and need to train it to
我们知道自己想使用人工神经网络
eventually have a system that will yield the correct output to a specific input.
所以需要训练该网络成为一个特定的系统 使其能生成与某个输入相对应的正确输出
Well correct most of the time.
至少大部分时候能生成正确输出
Essentially, what we really want is to find the optimal set of weights connecting
本质上 我们要做的就是找出一批最优权重
the input to the hidden layer and
将输入与隐藏层连接起来
the optimal set of weights connecting the hidden layer to the output.
再找出另一批最优权重 将隐藏层和输出连接起来
We will never have a perfect estimation but we can try to be as close to it as we can.
或许我们永远找不到完美的预测方案 但我们可以尽可能地接近完美